cenq.com 2011-06-24

# Creative Enquiry | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy of "cenq.com" (this "Site")**

This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Site and not necessarily to other cenq.com sites on the World Wide Web pages. When leaving this Site, please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. 

By accessing and using this Site, you hereby agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically:**  
cenq.com is committed to the protection of the privacy of its web site visitors. Please note that we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**Personal Information:**  
In order to respond to your questions, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail, e-mail or phone to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. However,unless compelled by applicable legislation, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs. You also hereby grant to cenq.com the right to exchange any information provided by you between cenq.com's affiliates for the purposes mentioned before. 

In addition to the personal information that you may provide us, this Site may use technology that lets us collect certain technical information like your Internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, traffic patterns and the address of any referring Web sites. 

**Security:**  
Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker- proof", cenq.com has endeavoured to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your personal information. For example, we use encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. 

**Accuracy of collected data:**  
cenq.com will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by cenq.com in connection with the operation of this Site. 

**Visitor identification:**  
From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as "cookies". By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to continue to improve our Site. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this Site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. 

**Log Files:**  
Like many other Web sites, cenq.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
cenq.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, . 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on cenq.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

cenq.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. cenq.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Minors:**  
No information may be submitted to cenq.com by persons under the age of 18 without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, nor may persons under the age of 18 make purchases or other legal acts on this Site without such consent, unless permitted by applicable legislation. 

**Changes:**  
We may change this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this Site, or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.
